If you're looking to avoid performative activism right now, the 5 Calls app might be helpful for
you. You can find it in the App Store. It's completely free and really easy to use.
So this is what it looks like in the App Store. This is what you're looking for.
And once you get it open, it'll look like this. You can just swipe on over and hit get started.
It'll show you immediately a bunch of issues. The one you want is right at the top.
And it'll give you some information about that issue with lots of links in case you
want to click out and learn more. Once you get to the bottom, you can set your location,
go ahead and pop in your zip, and it will auto-populate your representatives. These are mine.
And if you just click one, it'll bring you over to this page, which gives you their number. And
you can click that. It'll dial for you. And it provides a script in case you don't know what
to say. I hope that's helpful. I'm going to leave Stitches and Duets on for this one. So if you
think it's helpful and your audience might want to hear it too, do your thing. Do your thing, TikTok.